Guide to the Samuel C. G. Watkins Autograph Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Inventory
  - Landon, Alfred Mossman, 1887- (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lang, Cosmo Gordon, abp. Of York, 1864-1945 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lansing, Robert, 1864-1928 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Larson, Morgan F, 1882-1961 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Latane, John Holladay, 1869-1932 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lavery, John, 1845-1941 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Law, Andrew Bonar, 1858-1923 (2) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lawrence, Richard Wesley, 1878-1948 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Leahy, William D, 1875-1949 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Leffingwell, Russell Cornell, 1878-1960 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lehlbach, Frederick Reimold, 1876-1937 (4) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lehlbach, Herman, 1845-1904 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lenroot, Irvine Luther, 1869-1949 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lent, Frederick, 1872-1942 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Leslie, Harry Guyer, 1878-1937 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lewis, James Hamilton, 1863-1939 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lewis, John Llewellyn, 1880- (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lincoln, Robert Todd, 1843-1926 (2) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lindbergh, Charles Augustus, 1902- (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lindsay, Sir Ronald Charles, 1877-1945 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Linlithgow, Victor Alexander John Hope, 2nd marquis, 1887-1952 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Little, Clarence Cook, 1888- (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Liveright, Horace Brisbin, 1886-1933 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lloyd George, David Lloyd George, 1(st) earl, 1863-1945 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1850-1924 (3) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lofting, Hugh, 1886-1947 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Logan, James Addison, 1879- (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Longworth, Nicholas, 1869-1931 (2) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lord, Franklin Butler (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lorimer, George Horace, 1868-1937 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Loring, Augustus Peabody, 1856-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Low, Seth, 1850-1916 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lowden, Frank Orren, 1861-1943 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lowell, Abbott Lawrence, 1856-1943 (3) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lowell, Guy, 1870-1927 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lucas, Robert H, 1888-1947 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Luce, Robert Lee, 1862-1933 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lull, Richard Swann, 1867-1957 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lyon, Mary, 1797-1849 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - McAdoo, William Gibbs, 1863-1941 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - McArthur, Douglas, 1880-1964 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - McClellan, George S (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - McConaughy, James A, 1857-1934 (2) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - McCormick, Joseph Medill, 1877-1925 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - MacCracken, Henry Noble, 1880- (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - McCulloch, Roscoe Conkling, 1880-1958 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - McCumber, Porter James, 1858-1933 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Macfadden, Bernarr, 1868-1955 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - McFadden, Louis Thomas, 1876-1936 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - McGarrah, Gates W, 1863-1940 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - MacKay, Clarence Hungerford, 1874-1938 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - McKellar, Kenneth Douglas, 1869-1957 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - McKenzie, John Charles, 1860-1941 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - McKinley, William, Pres. U.S., 1843-1901 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - McKinley, William Brown, 1856-1926 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - McLean, George Payne, 1857-1932 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Macleod, W B (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - MacMillan, Donald Baxter, 1874- (2) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - MacMonnies, Frederick William, 1863-1937 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - McNary, Charles Linza, 1874-1944 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - McNeil, Samuel Giles Spencer, 1871-1936 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - McNeill, Ronald John, 1861- (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - McPherson, William, 1864-1951 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - McVay, Charles Butler, 1868-1968 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - MacVeagh, Charles, 1860-1931 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Madden, Martin Barnaby, 1855-1928 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Malone, Paul Bernard, 1872-1960 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Manning, Helen Herron (Taft), 1891- (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Manning, William Thomas, 1866-1949 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Marcus, Edwin (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Marvin, Cloyd Hick, 1889- (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mason, William Smith, 1866- (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Massey, Vincent, 1887-1967 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Masson, Thomas L, 1866-1934 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - May, Paul (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Meador, Elihu N (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mellon, Andrew William, 1855-1937 (2) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mencken, Henry Louis, 1880-1956 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Meyer, Eugene, 1875-1959 (2) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mezes, Sidney Edward, 1863-1931 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Miller, Nathan L, 1868-1953 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mills, Ogden Livingston, 1884-1937 (2) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Milner, Alfred Milner, 1(st) viscount, 1854-1925 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mitchell, Charles Edwin, 1877-1955 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mitchell, Edward Page, 1852-1927 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mitchell, William DeWitt, 1874- (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mondell, Franklin Wheeler, 1860-1939 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Moody, John, 1868-1958 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Moody, Paul Dwight, 1879-1947 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Moore, Frederick, 1877- (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Morgan, Arthur Ernest, 1878- (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Morgan, Ruth (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mormon Church autographs (no card) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Morris, Benjamin Wistar, 1870-1944 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Morris, Charles Gould, 1871-1961 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Morrow, Dwight Whitney, 1873-1931 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Morton, Levi Parsons, 1824-1920 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Moses, George Higgins, 1869-1944 (2) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mundelein, George William, cardinal, 1872-1939 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Murlin, Lenuel Herbert, 1861-1935 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Murray, William Henry, 1869-1956 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Nagel, Charles, 1849-1940 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Neilson, William Allan, 1869-1946 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Nelson, Knute, 1843-1923 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Nettleton, George Henry, 1874-1959 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - New, Harry Stewart, 1858-1937 (2) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Newberry, Truman Handy, 1864-1945 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Newell, Robert Henry, 1836-1901 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Newton, Walter Hughes, 1880-1941 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Nicholson, Samuel Danford, 1859-1923 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Norris, George William, 1861-1944 (2) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Northcliffe, Alfred Charles William Harmsworth, 1(st) baron, 1865-1922 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Notestein, Ada Louise (Comstock), 1876-1973 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Ochs, Adolph Simon, 1858-1935 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Oddie, Tasker Lowndes, 1870-1950 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Olds, George Daniel, 1853-1931 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Osborn, Henry Farifield, 1857-1935 (2) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Oswald, John Clyde, 1872-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Overman, Lee Slater, 1854-1930 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Owen, Robert Latham, 1856-1947 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Owen, Ruth Bryan, 1885-1954 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Page, Arthur Wilson, 1883-1960 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Palmer, Alexander Mitchell, 1872-1936 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Parker, Richard Wayne, 1848-1923 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Parker, Walter Henry, 1870- (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Parnell, Harvey, 1880-1936 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Partridge, Frank Charles, 1861-1943 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pearce, George Foster, 1870- (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pearson, Edward Jones, 1863-1928 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pell, Herbert Claiborn, 1884- (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pelley, John Jeremiah, 1878-1946 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pendleton, Ellen Fitz, 1864-1936 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Penniman, Josiah Harmar, 1868-1941 (3) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Penrose, Boies, 1860-1921 (2) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pepper, George Wharton, 1867-1961 (2) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Perlman, Nathan David, 1887-1952 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Perry, Henry Ten Eyck (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Perry, Lewis, 1877- (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pershing, John Joseph, 1860-1948 (3) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pew, J Howard (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Phelan, James Duval, 1861-1930 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Phelps, William Lyon, 1865-1943 (2) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Philips, Ralph (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Phillips, William, 1878-1951 (4) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Phipps, Lawrence Cowle, 1862-1958 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pickering, Nelson W (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pickering, William Henry, 1858-1938 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pillsbury, John Sargent, 1878-1968 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pinchot, Cornelia Elizabeth (Bryce), 1881-1960 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pinchot, Gifford, 1865-1946 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pittman, Key, 1872-1940 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Plantz, Samuel, 1859-1924 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Platt, Edmund, 1865-1939 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Platt, Thomas Collier, 1833-1910 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Plimpton, George Arthur, 1855-1936 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Poindexter, Miles, 1868-1946 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pole, John William (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Polk, Frank Lyon, 1871-1943 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pomerene, Atlee, 1863-1937 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Ponsonby, Arthur Augustus William Harry, 1871- (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Porter, Horace, 1837-1921 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Porter, Stephen Geyer, 1869-1930 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pratt, Ruth Sears (Baker), 1877- (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pratt, William Veazie, 1869- (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Proctor, Redfield, 1879-1957 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pupin, Michael Idvorsky, 1858-1935 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Putnam, George Haven, 1844-1930 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Ralston, Samuel Moffett, 1857-1925 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Ransdell, Joseph Eugene, 1858-1954 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Reed, Clyde Martin, 1871- (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Reed, David Aiken, 1880-1953 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Reed, Harvey Lathrop, 1867- (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Reed, James Alexander, 1861-1944 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Reid, Helen (Rogers), 1882- (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Reid, Ogden Mills, 1882-1947 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Reid, Whitelaw, 1837-1912 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Rhees, Rush, 1860-1939 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Rice, Richard Ashley, 1878-1955 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Richards, John Gardiner, 1864-1941 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Richey, Lawrence, 1885-1959 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Richmond, Charles Alexander, 1862-1940 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Riddle, John Wallace, 1864-1941 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Riggs, Charles Edward, 1869- (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Riis, Jacob August, 1849-1914 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Rinehart, Mary Roberts, 1876-1958 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Robbins, Howard, Chandler, 1876-1952 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Robertson, Gideon Decker, 1874- (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Robinson, Arthur Raymond, 1881-1961 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Robinson, Corinne (Roosevelt), 1861-1933 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Robinson, Fred Norris, 1871-1966 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Robinson, Frederick Bertrand, 1883-1941 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Robinson, Joseph Taylor, 1872-1937 (2) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Robinson, Kenneth Allan (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Rockefeller, John Davison, 1874-1960 (2) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Roebling, Washington Augustus, 1837-1926 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Rogers, James Grafton, 1883-1947 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor (Roosevelt), 1884-1962 (2) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Roosevelt, Edith Kermit (Carow), 1861-1948 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, Pres. U.S., 1882-1945 (3) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Roosevelt, Kermit, 1889-1943 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Roosevelt, Nicholas, 1893-1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, Pres. U.S., 1858-1919 (2) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1887-1944 (3) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Root, Elihu, 1845-1937 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Roper, Daniel Calhoun, 1867-1943 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Ross, Nellie (Tayloe), 1880- (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Russell, John Henry, 1872-1947 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Sage, Dean, 1876- (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Salisbury, James Edward Hubert Gascoyne Cecil, 4(th) marquis, 1861-1947 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sampson, Flem D, 1875-1967 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Schacht, Hjalmar, 1877- (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Schafer, John Charles, 1893-1962 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Schofield, Frank Herman, 1869-1942 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Schumann-Heink, Ernestine, 1861-1936 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Schurman, Jacob Gould, 1854-1942 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Schwab, Charles Michael, 1862-1939 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Selfridge, Harry Gordon, 1864-1947 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Seligman, Edwin Robert Anderson, 1861-1939 (2) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sembrich, Marcella, 1858-1935 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Seton, Ernest Thompson, 1860-1946 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Seymour, Charles, 1885-1963 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Shafer, George F, 1888-1948 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Shaw, Leslie Mortier, 1k48-1932 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sheffield, James Rockwell, 1864-1938 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sheppard, Morris, 1875-1941 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sherman, James Schoolcraft, 1855-1912 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sherrill, Henry Knox, 1890- (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Shipstead, Henrik, 1881-1960 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Shortridge, Samuel Morgan, 1861-1952 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Shotwell, James Thomson, 1874-1965 (2) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sievers, Frederick William, 1872- (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Simmons, Edward Henry Harriman, 1876-1955 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Simmons, Furnifold McLendel, 1854-1940 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Simon, John Allsebrook Simon, 1(st) viscount, 1873-1954 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sims, William Sowden, 1858-1936 (2) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sinclair, James Herbert, 1871- (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Slade, Caroline (McCormick), d. 1952 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sloan, Alfred Pritchard, 1875-1966 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Smith, Alfred Emanuel, 1873-1944 (3) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Smith, Ellison DuRant, 1864-1944 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Smith, Hoke, 1855-1931 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Smoot, Reed, 1862-1941 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Smuts, Jan Christiaan, 1870-1950 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Snowden, Philip Snowden, viscount, 1864-1937 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sousa, John Philip, 1854-1932 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Spaulding, Huntley Nowel, 1869- (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Spencer, Selden Palmer, 1862-1925 (2) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sperry, Willard Learoyd, 1882-1954 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sproule, William, 1858-1905 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Stanfield, Robert Nelson, 1877-1945 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Stanley, Augustus Owsley, 1867-1958 (2) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Stearns, Alfred Ernest, 1871-1949 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Stearns, Frank Waterman, 1856-1939 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Stephens, Hubert Durrett, 1875-1946 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sterling, Thomas, 1851-1930 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Stimson, Henry Lewis, 1867-1950 (2) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Studd, Sir John Edward Kynaston, 1858-1944 (2) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Stutz, Harry C, 1876-1930 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Styer, Freas (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sullivan, Mark, 1874-1952 (2) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sutherland, George Granville Leveson Gower, 5(th) duke of, 1888-1963 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sutherland, George, 1862-1942 (2) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sutherland, Howard, 1865-1950 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Swanson, Claude Augustus, 1862-1939 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Swope, Gerard, 1872-1957 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sydenham of Combe, George Sydenham Clark, baron, 1848-1933 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sykes, Richard Eddy, 1861-1942 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Taft, Henry Waters, 1859-1945 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Taft, Horace Dutton, 1861-1943 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Taft, William Howard, Pres. U.S., 1857-1930 (2) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Taylor, Myron Charles, 1874-1959 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Teagle, Walter Clark, 1878-1962 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Teller, Henry Moore, 1830-1914 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Temple, William, abp. Of Canterbury, 1881-1944 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Thomas, Augustus, 1857-1934 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Thomas, John Martin, 1869- (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Thomas, Norman Mattoon, 1884-1968 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Thorndike, Edward Lee, 1874-1949 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Tiffany, Louis Comfort, 1848-1933 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Tilson, John Quillin, 1866-1958 (4) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Tinker, Chauncey Brewster, 1876-1963 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Tinkham, George Holden, 1870-1956 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Tobey, Charles William, 1880- (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Traylor, Melvin Alvah, 1878-1934 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Trevelyan, Sir Charles Philips, 1870-1958 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Trumbull, John H, 1873-1961 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Tully, Thomas Allen, 1886-1950 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Tumulty, Joseph Patrick, 1879-1954 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Tunney, Gene, 1898- (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Turner, Raymond (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Underwood, Oscar Wilder, 1862-1929 (5) (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Untermyer, Samuel, 1858-1940 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Upham, Alfred Horatio, 1886-1945 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Upshaw, William David, 1866-1952 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Vance, Arthur Turner, 1872-1930 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Vanderlip, Frank Arthur, 1864-1937 (2) (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Van Dyke, Paul, 1859-1933 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Van Loon, Hendrik Willem, 1882-1944 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Van Sweringen, Mantis James, 1881-1935 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Villard, Fanny (Garrison), 1844-1928 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Villard, Oswald Garrison, 1872-1949 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Volstead, Andrew John, 1860-1947 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Wadhams, Albion Varette, 1847-1927 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wadsworth, James Wolcott, 1877-1952 (2) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wagner, Robert Ferdinand, 1877-1953 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Walcott, Charles Doolittle, 1850-1927 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Walcott, Frederic Collin, 1869-1949 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wallace, Henry Cantwell, 1866-1924 (2) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Walsh, David Ignatius, 1872-1947 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Walsh, Thomas James, 1859-1933 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wanamaker, John, 1838-1922 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Warburg, Felix M, 1871-1937 (2) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Warfield, David, 1866-1951 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Warren, Charles Hyde, 1876-1950 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Waterman, Charles Winfield, 1861-1932 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Waterlow, Sir William Alfred, 1867- (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Watson, James Eli, 1863-1948 (2) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Watson, Thomas John, 1874-1956 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Weaver, Arthur J, 1873-1945 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Webster, Daniel, 1782-1852 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Weller, Ovington Eugene, 1862-1947 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wellman, Walter, 1858-1934 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Werlich, McCeny (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Weygandt, Cornelius, 1871-1957 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wheeler, Burton Kendall, 1882- (2) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wheeler, Wayne Bidwell, 1869-1927 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - White, Alma Bridwell, 1862-1946 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - White, Henry, 1850-1927 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - White, Wallace Humphrey, 1877-1952 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - White, Sir William Thomas, 1866-1957 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - White, William Allen, 1868-1944 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Whitlock, Brand, 1869-1934 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Whitney, Richard, 1888- (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wickersham, George Woodward, 1858-1936 (3) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wiggam, Albert Edward, 1871-1957 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman, 1875-1949 (2) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Williams, Arthur, 1868-1937 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Williams, Jesse Lynch, 1871-1929 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Williams, John Sharp, 1854-1932 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Williams, Ralph E, 1870-1940 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Willingdon, Freeman Freeman-Thomas, 1(st) viscount, 1866-1941 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Willis, Frank Bartlett, 1871-1928 (3) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wills, Helen Newington, 1906- (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wilson, Edith. (Bolling) Galt, 1872-1961 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wilson, Hugh Robert, 1885-1946 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wilson, Sir Leslie Orme, 1876- (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wilson, Margaret Woodrow, 1886-1944 (2) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wilson, Stanley Calef, 1879- (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wilson, Woodrow, Pres. U.S., 856-1924 (2) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Winant, John Gilbert, 1889-1967 (2) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wing, Daniel Gould, 1868-1936 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Winslow, Samuel Ellsworth, 1862-1940 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Winnington-Ingrain, Arthur Foley, bp. of London, 1858-1946 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wise, Stephen Samuel, 1874-1949 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wishart, Charles Frederick (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wolcott, Josiah Oliver, 1877-1938 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wood, Leonard, 1860-1927 (3) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wood, William Robert, 1861-1933 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Woodring, Harry Hines, 1890-1967 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Woodruff, George Catlin (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Woods, Cyrus E, 1861-1938 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Woolley, Mary Emma, 1863- (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Work, Hubert, 1860-1942 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wright, Herbert E, 1872-1943 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wrigley, William, 1861-1932 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Yerkes, Robert Meares, 1876-1956 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Yoshida, Kwan (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Young, Allyn Abbott, 1876-1929 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Young, Clarence Marshall, 1889- (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Young, Clement Calhoun, 1869-1947 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Young, Josephine (Edmonds) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Young, Owen D, 1874-1962 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - [Unidentified] (Box 3, Folder 25)